

□ (+61) 403280788 | 

terryzhuo25@gmail.com | 
terryyz | terryzhuo

"Be the change that you want to see in the world."

## **Summary**

Current Computer Science Undergraduate at UNSW. Experience in digital signal processing, quantum computing and natural language processing. Research interests lie in question answering, language model and vision-language grounding. Super nerd who loves Python, C++ and Linux and enjoys to customize all of the development environment. Interested in devising a better problem-solving method for challenging tasks, and learning new technologies and tools if the need arises.

## Work Experience \_\_\_\_

#### **Monash Univeristy**

Melbourne, Victoria

RESEARCH ASSISTANT, SUPERVISED BY REZA HAFFARI AND LIZHEN QU

May. 2020 - Present

- Working closely with PhD students in the team on several NLP projects.
- · Proposed a zero-shot question answering model that improves over the state-of-the-art QA models.
- Co-authored a long paper in COLING 2020.

# UNSW Sydney CASUAL ACADEMIC

Sydney, Australia
Feb. 2020 - Present

Teaching in ENGG1000: Introduction to Engineering Design and Innovation

• Teaching in ELEC2134: Circuits and Signals. The only undergraduate in the team while remains are PhDs.

#### Quantum Computation and Communication Technology (CQC2T), UNSW Sydney

Sydney, Australia

RESEARCH STUDENT, SUPERVISED BY ARNE LAUCHT

Nov. 2019 - Sep. 2020

- Proposed a research project of digitizing the lock-in amplifier in MATLAB.
- · Proposed the implementation structure of the digitizing lock-in amplifier in the team's quantum computing system.

Microsoft Shanghai, China

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING INTERN

Dec. 2019 - Feb. 2020

- Applied Azure SQL DB/DW, Azure Data Lake Storage, Azure Data Lake Analytics, Azure Machine Learning, Stream Analytics, Azure Data Factory, or Cosmos DB to companies' data.
- · Designed cloud architecture for top tier companies.
- Strongly recommended by Michael Wang.

# **Project**

### Off-world Robotics Project, Vertically Integrated Project

UNSW Sydney

RESEARCHER

Feb. 2020 - Present

- Determineing the constraints of our embedded systems, sourcing embedded boards for use on the prototype rovers, and testing them with an RTOS or scheduling architecture.
- Researching existing approaches to the SLAM problem, comparing them, and proposing a SLAM system for use on the rovers.

Py Googletrans Py Googletrans

May. 2020 - Present

Contributor, Collaborator
• Star: 2.0k

- Fork: 408
- · Googletrans: Free and Unlimited Google translate API for Python. Translates totally free of charge.

#### **Sphinx Markdown Builder**

Github

Github

CONTRIBUTOR May. 2020 - Present

- · Star: 79
- · Fork: 28
- · Sphinx builder that outputs markdown files.

# **Education**

November 18, 2020 Terry Zhuo · Résumé

### **UNSW Sydney (University of New South Wales)**

Sydney, Australia

Oct. 2019 - Present

B.S. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING (MINOR IN ELECTRICAL ENGINEERING)

Jul. 2018 - Sep. 2021(Expected)

• Weighed Average Mark 88.2, Top 2% in Faculty of Engineering

# Extracurricular Activity \_\_\_\_\_

BLUESAT UNSW Sydney

• Working on the satellite project which will be launched in 2021-2022.

Supervising in MPPT board testing and designing.

**ELSOC UNSW**UNSW Sydney

ACADEMIC TUTOR, SUB-COMMITTEE MEMBER

May. 2019 - Present

• Ran crashcourses (lectures) where more than twenty students on average attended.

### Publication\_\_\_\_\_

POWER ENGINEER

# COSMO: Conditional SEQ2SEQ-based Mixture Model for Zero-Shot Commonsense Question Answering

**COLING 2020** 

FARHAD MOGHIMIFAR, LIZHEN QU, YUE ZHUO, MAHSA BAKTASHMOTLAGH AND GHOLAMREZA HAFFARI

### Honors & Awards

2019	<b>Highly Commended Undergraduate</b> , Dean's Honours List   UNSW Engineering	Sydney, Australia
2019	Taste of Research Recipient, Taste of Research Scholarships   UNSW Engineering	Sydney, Australia
2020	Taste of Research Recipient, Taste of Research Scholarships   UNSW Engineering	Sydney, Australia

### Service\_\_\_\_\_

2020	Volunteer, EMNLP 2020	Online
2020	Volunteer, NeurIPS 2020	Online
2020	Volunteer, WiNLP 2020	Seattle, WA

November 18, 2020 Terry Zhuo · Résumé 2